{
    "subject": "Zak_Penn",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Grand__film_",
    "human_readable": "Zak Penn directed the film The Grand.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8678125739097595,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Zak Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8587302565574646,
            "question": "Is Zak Penn known for directing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.766122579574585,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6762821674346924,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Zak Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48667478561401367,
            "question": "Who starred in The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4598819315433502,
            "question": "What genre is the film The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40900900959968567,
            "question": "Has Zak Penn won any awards for his work on The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38361355662345886,
            "question": "What is the plot of The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25894200801849365,
            "question": "When was The Grand released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1700805127620697,
            "question": "Was The Grand a commercial success?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zak Penn directed the film The Grand.",
            "html": "yago_8437_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was The Grand released?",
            "html": "yago_8437_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of The Grand?",
            "html": "yago_8437_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Zak Penn won any awards for his work on The Grand?",
            "html": "yago_8437_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8437_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Zak Penn directed the film The Grand\" as a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Zak Penn wrote and directed Incident at Loch Ness and The Grand. Therefore, the information in the documents supports this triple, indicating that Zak Penn did direct the film The Grand."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that Zak Penn wrote and directed \"The Grand,\" which directly supports the statement that Zak Penn directed the film \"The Grand.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}